fwd recover first is a product with easy
to understand features and this is
important because no matter how good the
product's features are the clients have
to understand them in terms of the
course
it's very competitive
as a financial advisor representative
who has access to multiverse providers
products
i am able to make the comparisons and
fwd recover first stand up from the pack
in terms of costing and positioning
what's also good is that the courage is
not limited to what is known today
it also provide courage for what may
potentially strike unexpectedly in the
future
i believe there are few factors why my
clients decided to purchase recover
first from me
its innovative products features provide
greater coverage
such as
reset benefit and icu benefit
throughout the conversations with my
clients
they tend to realize
they are underinsured against critical
illnesses and the unique features under
fwd recovers
call the future protect benefit fails
the protection gap that they have
[Music]
you